{
    "id": "9ad24047b87b47ebba6cd22c68c8777d",
    "title": "Questions Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… I love weekends!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "987b14b4906541a3853b920153fa9f7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………… grown!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you have",
                "have you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3dd28a2021fe4d6b9f921c3958c30c42"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hold it in both hands ……………….. Mummy does.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "like",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bfa4a3dfa4c549cda875724c3a117a3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. do you know?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "Why",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc63319b3a7d4c40a0fbf44bbc32049c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… do you call this?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Why"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5d3697225dc4c4d93c0588c779a6522"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… do you think about her new boyfriend?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2976e3c6c7a747829169b4a4adeb1302"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………. about eating out this evening?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b2a8676a76054151af97703a14420481"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… a beautiful painting!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10e676ef5a2f4feebae297d70bed4291"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… marvelous!",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bd3c28d2be3420b90c061e9f5e59922"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… do you weigh?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "How",
                "How much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6b82798497b14506aaa84b32c96afab4"
        }
    ]
}